If you've been paying attention, you know I'm back on tour.
Get your tickets at amandaseals.com.
And my first two shows were in Chicago, and I stayed at the Langham.
I love the Langham Chicago for several reasons.
One, because, I mean, it's just classy.
You know what I'm saying?
Look at all the gold.
Look at all these white chairs.
Look at this giant sculpture.
You already know it's going to be something nice.
When you open the door, light bathes the room.
You got all these seating options.
I don't know about y'all, but I love different options to sit on.
And I love a view.
And who doesn't love a little bit of champs and a little welcome note?
Hey, Chicago.
Now, one thing I haven't done when I sit at the Langham is go to their spa.
And I don't know why, because I need to be at the spa.
Your girl needs to relax.
And that is what I did.
Look at the digs.
Marble, honey.
I slid in them slides, put on my robe, and I was ready to be pampered.
Look at the decor.
It just lets you know we've got to take care of you.
Came and sat in the spa waiting room.
They had like a waterfall thing.
Anytime you see cool tiles, it lets you know something's about to go down.
And this was the room where I had my massage.
It just felt like all my chakras were about to be like, ah.
And honey, they were.
That's the sunset on another beautiful trip to Chicago.
And thank you to the Langham and the staff who were all absolutely delightful and truly understand the meaning of hospitality.
Tell them I said hi when you dropped by the Langham Chicago.
up.